[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "But they have been released, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Yes, exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "How dangerous is this situation, how easy is it now to create a ricin scare?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "Well, Piers, we should start by reminding people, look, there have been inconsistent preliminary tests, those field tests are typically inaccurate, which is why they sent it to the lab.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Is the FBI investigating it now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "The FBI is investigating it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "How deadly could they be, potentially, in the wrong hands?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "Worst-case scenario, it can be terribly deadly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "How easy is it for somebody, a regular Joe in the street, to sit down, get on the computer, go to his local store, and create deadly ricin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VB", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Unfortunately, it's easier than a lot of other potential bio agents.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Because of this particular threat, apparently targeting politicians, mayors, because of their position on gun control, will the other thousand mayors who have been signing up to this, will they now have to be properly protected more than they are already?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "DT", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "RBR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Well, there's no question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Chad, what's the latest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "Well, it just started raining here, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Do you believe it's getting worse?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "I believe it's getting more severe in both directions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Have we had these before in the last 30 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "We have had these before.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 30 years?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "What is a skeptical environmentalist?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "Well, fundamentally, it's the guy that say, yes, there are environmental problems and global warming is real.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill"]}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "Is that accurate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Fundamentally, yes, Bill.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "Do you believe that global warming is a real and present situation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Yes, and humans are responsible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["U.N. Climate Panel"]}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "And to you, Bjorn, believe that as a consequence of that, there could be any effect whatsoever on the power or the volume of tornadoes, hurricanes or big storms?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "If you look at the U.N. Climate Panel, they have done a lot of surveys on a lot of these different studies.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bjorn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Why would anybody do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Well, I just wanted to protect my rights, my Second Amendment rights.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "PRP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 320, "question": "Do you know how many?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Well, to me, what I worry about, Piers --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Ones that you could go and buy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "I'm sure the number is high.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "What is the number?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "Have a guess.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Would you arm every school, every hospital, every church, every shopping mall, every person that works in those places?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "No, that was an NRA statement, by the way, and I never necessarily agreed with it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "England"]}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "When that happens seriously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Well, you say what's wrong with America, but your home country of England has basically banned handguns in the hands of law abiding citizens.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "How many of those -- how many of those school children would have been killed if Adam Lanza had a rope at Sandy Hook?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Well, if guns are the reason for Sandy Hook and all these problems, I think we should disarm Barack Obama's security force.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adam Lanza"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "But why do you believe that President Obama should be impeached over it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Well, I didn't say he should be impeached unless we prove that it went to him.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "I think all politicians should be limited to two terms, one term in office and one term in prison.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "Do you think of one actual fact she has come up with has turned out to be true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "Well, I don't worry about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Is that a charge with which you would find the country guilty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "How old were you when that happened and what were you feeling?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "DT", "VBN", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "I was feeling suicidal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "And Glenn, were you aware of any of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "That's the amazing thing, is really kind of basic to our message.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Glenn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "For those who have no idea what a bipolar condition is, what is the simple, layman's way of describing it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "You have very, very low lows, depression, it used to be called manic depression, which is more descriptive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "What persuaded you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Those facts that there are so many people living with this that don't have a voice and I think it's important that they know that there's other people out there like them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "Have you spoken to either of them about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "No, I haven't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "And it can be a happy situation that you come through to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "Yes, it can be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130529pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "What was your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Huge respect.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]